<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="service.subtitles.relay"
       name="Relay Subtitles"
       version="0.1.18"
       provider-name="aziz66">
  <requires>
    <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
    <import addon="script.module.relay" version="0.1.2"/>
    <import addon="plugin.video.relay" version="0.1.1"/>
  </requires>
  <extension point="xbmc.subtitle.module" library="service.py"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.service" library="autodownload.py"/>
  <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
    <summary lang="en_GB">Subtitles from your Stremio addons</summary>
    <description lang="en_GB">During playback, searches every configured Stremio addon that declares a 'subtitles' resource (shared with Relay) for the currently playing IMDB title and offers the results in Kodi's subtitle dialog.</description>
    <platform>all</platform>
    <license>GPL-3.0-or-later</license>
    <news>v0.1.18 - Auto-download now RETRIES the subtitle search (within the id window) instead of giving up after one try, so a binge into the next episode reliably loads your language instead of keeping Kodi's embedded forced track.
v0.1.17 - URL-decode the playing filename before parsing (AIOStreams &amp; other sources percent-encode it), so titles like "The Punisher One Last Kill" resolve.
v0.1.16 - Better filename identification: strip scene site-tags and accept a Cinemeta match on year + name-contained-in-filename, so messy release names (e.g. "...A Marvel Television Special Presentation -- The Punisher One Last Kill 2026...") resolve. Icon at add-on root.
v0.1.14 - GPL license, disclaimer; Cinemeta filename resolver; boot-race retry.</news>
    <disclaimer lang="en_GB">Relay is an independent project and is not affiliated with, endorsed by, or associated with the Kodi/XBMC Foundation or Stremio. It ships no media, content or stream sources - it only presents add-ons that you choose to install. Do not use it for piracy or to access content you are not authorised to.</disclaimer>
    <assets>
      <icon>icon.png</icon>
    </assets>
  </extension>
</addon>
